Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Moral Values and The Fast Buck, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Ralph Helstein. Address given by Helstein before the Fourth Biennial Conference of the United Packinghouse Workers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor's Decisive Decade, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By James B. Carey. An address given by Carey. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: AFL-CIO Codes of Ethical Practices, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The Role of the AFL-CIO Ethical Practices Committee, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Al Hayes. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Social Justice Award to the AFL-CIO Ethical Practices Committee, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Cameron P. Hall; John C. Cort; Eugene J. Lipman; Albert J. Hayes. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Disposition of Matters Referred to the Executive Council, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
    By Canadian Labour Congress. Item is in English; French.
  - Item 12: The Values We Cherish, Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at Congress 1977, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
    By AFL-CIO, Department of Legislation. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Congressional Voting Record First Session, 98th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The People's Lobby: An AFL-CIO Report on the 96th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Democratic Presidential Candidates: Views on Labor Issues, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Labor Looks at Congress 1978, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Labor Looks at the 94th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at Congress 1973, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Labor Looks at Congress 1975, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Labor Looks at the 92nd Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Labor Looks at the 93rd Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Washington Pressures: Public Worker's Union to Test Political Clout in Washington, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Charles Culhane. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Check it With Strom?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Southern Wage Earners Information Center. December 27, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Looks at Congress 1969, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Labor Looks at the 91st Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Labor Looks at Congress 1971, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Labor Looks at the 89th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Labor Looks at Congress 1965, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Labor Looks at Congress 1967, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Labor Looks at the 90th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: A Window on the Labor Press, Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
    By Eleanor H. Scanlan. Reprinted from "Michigan Business Review" Vol. XIX, No. 3. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Labor Looks at the 88th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Labor and the Elections, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Do You Believe in Majority Rule?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By Michigan State AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Resolution Endorsing the Candidacy of President Lyndon B. Johnson, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By International Association of Bridge, Structural & Ornamental Iron Workers. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: California Labor Council on Political Education, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
    By California Labor Council. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Union Political Activity Spans 230 Years of U.S. History, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Labor Looks at the 87th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Labor Looks at Congress 1963, Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Analysis of the Federal Law Governing Political Expenditures by Labor Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Gall, Lane and Howe. May 23, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Man and Climate in the Eisenhower Era, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Inter-Union Institute, Inc. "Labor and Nation Timely Papers" Vol. 1, No. 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor Looks at the 85th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Labor Looks at Congress 1959, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Organized Labor and Political Action in Colorado: 1900-1960, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By George E. Bardwell; Harry Seligson. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Reaching the Voter: The 1956 Pentland Campaign, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
    By Teamsters Local 688. January 27, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Labor Looks at the 86th Congress, Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Labor and the World Crisis, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Ernest Bevin; Leon Jouhaux; Matthew Woll. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: India, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By George Ridley. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Labor in Politics, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Political Consciousness in Local Union, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Joel Seidman. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Investigation of Un-American Activities and Propganda, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By U.S. Congress, Special Committee on Un-American Activities. Union Calendar No. 2; House Report No. 2; 76th Congress, 1st Session; January 3, 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Signs of the Times, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Memorandum of the Washington Dinner on Labor's Part in the Administration of the War, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By National Policy Committee. "National Policy Memoranda" No. 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What is PAC, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By CIO, Poltical Action Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Speaks for Itself!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Workers Education Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Labor Leader: A Story of Preogressive Unionism, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Glen Dale Carothers. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: PAC - Spearhead for Dictatorship, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    By Fred W. Blaisdell. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Gaining Access to Radio and TV Time: A union Member's Guide to the Broadcast Media, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By AFSCME. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Public Relations for Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Public Relations Plan for Local Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    By AFL-CIO, Public Employee Department. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: American Trade Union Journals and Labor Papers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. List of publications. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Program and Proceedings of the 8th Annual Labor Editors Conference, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    By Rutgers University. April 20, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Management Consultant Looks at the Labor Press, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    By Robert Newcomb; Marg Sammons. Lecture series no. 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Automation in the Labor Press, Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    By Frederic M. Scholar. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The World of Labor, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By Francis Gates. Checklist of current labor union publications. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Third Annual Conference for Labor Journal Editors, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. April 22-23, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Canadian Labour Press From 1867: A Chronological Annotated Directory, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By Robbins L. Elliott. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: How to be a Union Reporter, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By International Woodworker. October 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Winning Your Readers' Interest, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. Report from the 5th annual Labor Journal Editors' Conference on May 23-24, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Give Your Readers a Break!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. Proceedings from 4th annual Labor Journal Editor's Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Proceedings from Conference of Labor Journal Editors, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. April 23-24, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report of Proceedings Conference of Editors of Labor Journals, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. March 28-29, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Notebook for Labor Journalism Conference, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. February 26, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What's Wrong with Labor Papers?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By Sam Sherman. Speech delivered by Sam Sherman at the Conference on Labor Papers on March 1-2, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: American Trade Union Journals and Labor Papers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 12: American Trade Union Journals and Labor Papers Currently Received by the Department of Labor Library, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Summary of a Conference on Labor Papers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Wisconsin. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Labor Press Directory, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By International Labor Press Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: American Independent Labor Journals in the University of Illinois Library, Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
    By University of Illinois. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Recreation in a Labor Setting, Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
    By Ruth March. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: First Conference with Research Directors of National and International Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. June 27-28, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Proceedings from Second Annual Conference with Research Directors of National and International Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. June 19-20, 1941. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Proceedings from Third Annual Conference with Research Directors of National and International Unions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
    By U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics. June 17-18, 1942. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Minutes of Evidence 12, Witness Mr. Cyril Grunfeld, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
    By Royal Commission on Trade Unions and Employers' Associations. Tuesday 21st December 1965. Item is in English.
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Wanted - Improved Labor Leadership, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By William D. Rawlins. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unions and the Problems of Working People, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By Arthur Kornhauser. Fifth lecture in series on Industrial Relations; February 28, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Morality in Unions and Business, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By Harry Seligson. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Nature of Trade Union Power, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By James Roosevelt. "Labor in Mid-America Series" No. 2; Address before 14th Annual Shop Conference on January 27, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Unions in the Community, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    By University of Minnesota. Proceedings of a Conference on February 15-16, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Union Powers and Workers' Rights, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Economic Implications of Union Power, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Legal and Moral Basis of Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By J. C. Gibson. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: "Right to Work" Laws - A Trap for America's Minorities, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Bayard Rustin. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: What They Say About 'Right-to-Work' Laws, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Labor Standards are Lower in 'Right to Work' States, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: The AFL-CIO Case for Repeal of 14(b), Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Congress Asked: Save 14(b), Testimony Before House Labor Group, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Kenneth C. Kellar. June 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Opposing Repeal of Section 14(b) of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By National Electrical Manufacturers Association. June 3, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Repeal of Section 14(b) - Fact or Fiction?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Wayne Morse. Speech given on January 28, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: What Price Compulsory Unionism?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By C. W. Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Cartoonist and Your Right to Work, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By National Right to Work Committee. Collection of political cartoons. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The "Right-to-Work" Issue, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Dale G. Brickner; Higdon C. Roberts. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Union Security and Right-To-Work, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By U.S. Department of Labor. Selected readings and references. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: 'Right to Work' Laws Lower Labor Standards, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 14: A Look at the Facts on Right-to-Work Laws, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Eastern Conference of Teamsters. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: 14(b) and Your Freedom to Work to Manage, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 16: Union Security the Case against the Compulsory Open Shop, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 17: What Do You Tell Them About 14(b)?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 18: 'Right to Work' Laws Lower Labor Standards, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 19: The History of 14(b) and What It Means, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 20: The Legal Case Against 14(b), Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 21: Exposed: Union Myths about Right to Work, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Box 14, Folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Right to Work: A Brief Study, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: News Release on Forbes Survey on Indiana's "right-to-work" law, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By National Council for Industrial Peace. October 14, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Reprints of Articles, Speeches and Court Decisions Regarding Compulsory Union Membership, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: A Bibliography of Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: America's Choice: Right to Work or Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By National Right to Work Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Report to Management: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By General Electric. April 5, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Case for Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: "Right to Work" Laws: Some Economic and Ethical Aspects, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
    By William James Lee. Abstract of a dissertation. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: In 'Right to Work' States Labor Standards are Lower, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Right to Work Laws and the common Good, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Should It Be Illegal to Require Union Membership as a Condition of Employment?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Congressional Digest. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Monograph Discussing the Major Aspects of the Intercollegiate Debate Issue "Resolved: That the Requirement of Membership in a Labor Organization as a Condition of Employment Should Be Illegal", Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By National Associational of Manufacturers. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Right-to-Work Laws and Economic Growth Are They "Right-to-Wreck" Laws?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Missouri State Chamber of Commerce. Research Report No. 33; August 7, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Right-to-Work Issue, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: How Right to Work Was Adopted in Kansas, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Reed Larson. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Bibliography of Right to Work Movement and Related Anti-Labor Legislation 1941-1957, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Richard J. Patterson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Selected References, Pro and Con: The "Right to Work", Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By U.S. Chamber of Commerce. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The "Right-to-Work" Issue: Pro's and Con's, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Leonard Wigon; Bilbert E. Donahue. Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Union Security vs Compulsory Unionism: The "Right to Work" Issue, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By University of Illinois. "Labor-Management Relations" Vol. 9, No. 1; A list of selected readings for high schools. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Morally Sound: Religious Leaders View the Union Shop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO, Industrial Union Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Case for Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: The Case for the Union Shop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Good for Business An Employer Views the Union Shop, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By John I. Snyder, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Union Shopping, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Maurice R. Franks. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Lanny K. Walker. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Compulsory Union Membership Un-Americanism at Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By McLellan Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Voluntary Unionism for Free Americans, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By John E. Coogan. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Union Shop and the Public Welfare, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By AFL-CIO, Industrial Union Department. Proceedings of the second annual Industrial Relations Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Forced Union Membership Steals Your Freedom!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 20: Warning! Danger Ahead!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: The Legal and Moral Basis of Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By J. C. Gibson. Address by Gibson. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Union Shop: The Achilles Heel of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By The State Publishing Co. Comic book style pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Creed and Pledges of the "Majority" of Organized "Right-to-Work" Advocates, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 24: The Right-to-Work Handbook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By William Ingles. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Right to Work Laws and the Common Good, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 26: The I.B.E.W. Looks at Restrictive Labor Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By IBEW. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: The Right to Work: Our Hottest Labor Issue, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By W. L. White. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Right-to-Work Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By William R. McIntyre. "Editorial Research Reports" Vol. II, No. 19; November 13, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: The Right to Work is The Right to Live, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Ernest M. Sims. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: "Right to Work" in Practice, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Frederic Meyers. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Why Right-to-Work Laws are a Necessity, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Martin Lu. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Right-to-Work Law Issues: An Evidentiary Approach, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Daniel H. Pollitt. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Should a Man Have to Join a Union to Work?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    By Charles A. Kothe. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By General Electric. May 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Security: The "Right-to-Work" Controversy, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By AFL-CIO. "Labor's Economic Review" Vol. 1, No.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Background for Decision on Voluntary Union Membership, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By U.S. Chamber of Commerce. Collection of articles appearing in Washington Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Constitution and The Right to Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Do Right to Work Laws Hurt or Help the Economy?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Maintenance-of-Membership and Other Measures for Union Security: Selected References, 1941-1945, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Edna L. Stone. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union Security, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Princeton University. "Selected References" No. 14; Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Right-to-Work Laws and Fundamental Freedoms, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Leo Wolman. Address delivered on December 9, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Injustice on Trial, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By AFL-CIOAFL-CIO, Department of Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What is Behind the So-Called "Right to Work" Bill?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Baltimore Federation of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Right to Shirk?, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Jerome L. Toner. Address given on February 18, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Why of a Right-to-Work Law, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: How "Right-to-Work" Laws are Passed: Florida Sets the Pattern, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By John G. Shott. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Legal and Moral Basis of Right to Work Laws, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By J. C. Gibson. Address given by Gibson on August 23, 1955; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Twenty Questions about the Right-to-Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Union Security, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Orme W. Phelps. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Right to Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Dumas Malone. "Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science" Vol. XXVI, No. 1; Series of addresses and papers presented on April 21, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Case for Voluntary Unionism, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: "Right-to-Work" Laws: Three Moral Studies, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By William J. Kelley; Israel Goldstein; Walter G. Muelder. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Security, Civil Liberties and Unions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Harry Fleischman; Joyce Lewis Kornbluh; Benjamin D. Segal. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Involuntary Participation in Unionism, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
    By Philip D. Bradley. Item is in English.
- Box 15, Folder (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Building a Strong Union, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
    By The Newspaper Guild. Item is in English.